zolved.com 2009-05-02

# Zolved - privacy policy - Support and help for problems with iPods, computers, XBox, email, cell phones, PDAs, wireless networks, game consoles and Windows Vista

ZOLVED takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how ZOLVED treats personal information that ZOLVED collects and receives, including information related to your past use of ZOLVED services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name or e-mail address, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

Information Collection and Use

General

  * ZOLVED collects personal information when you register with ZOLVED and use the ZOLVED service. ZOLVED may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name and e-mail address. Once you register with ZOLVED and sign up for our service, you are not anonymous to us.
  * ZOLVED collects information about your transactions with us.
  * ZOLVED automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, ZOLVED cookie information, and the pages you requested.
  * ZOLVED uses information for the following general purposes: to customize and personalize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you for feedback and conduct research.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * ZOLVED does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ZOLVED terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if ZOLVED is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ZOLVED will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Cookies

  * ZOLVED may set and access ZOLVED cookies on your computer.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

General

  * You can edit your ZOLVED Account Information at any time.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the ZOLVED service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your ZOLVED account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your ZOLVED account by send us an email.

Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * ZOLVED may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ZOLVED account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Questions and Suggestions

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please give us feedback or send us an email at [feedback@zolved.com](mailto:feedback@zolved.com?subject=Feedback)

ZOLVED™ is a service from IPTouch Inc.

IPTouch Inc.

4677 Old Ironsides Drive #370  
Santa Clara, CA 95054  
USA Phone: (408) 748-1707  
Fax: (650) 249-0435
